final Map<String, Map<String, List<Map<String, dynamic>>>> medicalQuestions = {
  'Medical': {
    'Anatomy': [
      {
        'question': 'Which organ is part of the central nervous system?',
        'options': ['Heart', 'Brain', 'Liver', 'Kidney'],
        'answer': 'Brain',
      },
      {
        'question': 'Which bone is the longest in the human body?',
        'options': ['Skull', 'Femur', 'Rib', 'Humerus'],
        'answer': 'Femur',
      },
      {
        'question': 'Which muscle is responsible for breathing?',
        'options': ['Biceps', 'Diaphragm', 'Hamstring', 'Triceps'],
        'answer': 'Diaphragm',
      },
    ],
    'Physiology': [
      {
        'question': 'Which organ regulates blood sugar?',
        'options': ['Heart', 'Pancreas', 'Kidney', 'Stomach'],
        'answer': 'Pancreas',
      },
      {
        'question': 'What carries oxygen in the blood?',
        'options': ['White blood cells', 'Hemoglobin', 'Platelets', 'Plasma'],
        'answer': 'Hemoglobin',
      },
      {
        'question': 'What is homeostasis?',
        'options': ['Body’s growth process', 'Internal balance maintenance', 'Cell death', 'Muscle contraction'],
        'answer': 'Internal balance maintenance',
      },
    ],
    'Pharmacology': [
      {
        'question': 'What is the function of antibiotics?',
        'options': ['Reduce pain', 'Kill or stop bacteria', 'Lower sugar', 'Cure viral infections'],
        'answer': 'Kill or stop bacteria',
      },
      {
        'question': 'Which route is fastest for drug absorption?',
        'options': ['Oral', 'Intravenous', 'Topical', 'Rectal'],
        'answer': 'Intravenous',
      },
      {
        'question': 'Paracetamol is mainly used for:',
        'options': ['High blood pressure', 'Fever and pain relief', 'Asthma', 'Diabetes'],
        'answer': 'Fever and pain relief',
      },
    ],
    'Medical Ethics': [
      {
        'question': 'Patient confidentiality means:',
        'options': ['Doctors share info with family', 'Medical info kept private', 'Post info on web', 'No diagnosis'],
        'answer': 'Medical info kept private',
      },
      {
        'question': 'What is informed consent?',
        'options': ['Patient agrees after full information', 'Doctor’s permission', 'Family request', 'Legal document'],
        'answer': 'Patient agrees after full information',
      },
      {
        'question': 'One of the four main bioe;thics principles is:',
        'options': ['Profit', 'Autonomy', 'Speed', 'Ranking'],
        'answer': 'Autonomy',
      },
    ],
  }
};